We need to talk
About the project
Go find the Su Group and the bank
It's not about the project Ming Yao
It's about 15 years ago
Why did you never tell me
Tell you what
That you helped him
Gu Chengze do you think
If I told you earlier
That he might be connected to the Fu family
You would have made a different choice
Don't tell me you chose Fu Chenzhou
Without considering the benefits
Mr Gu
When she chose me
I was just the bodyguard you mentioned
She knew the past
But didn't use it to tie me down
She knew the Fu family was investigating
But didn't use them to force me
A choice you couldn't make
Doesn't mean she can't
Please leave Mr Gu
Fu Chenzhou you haven't returned to the Fu family yet
Do you really think you've won
Whether I have won or not
Is not up to the Fu family
When she stood by my side
I had already won once
Were you serious about what you just said
Which part
Me standing by your side